deepenglish.com 2010-06-03

# 

Deep English takes your privacy very seriously. We guarantee that all of your personal information – any other other information you pass along to us – is private, safe, and strictly confidential. Reading this privacy policy will help you make informed decisons when using our site, products, and services.

**The Kind of Information We Collect**  
We collect information from you in order to provide you with a more customized service, which we think our learners will appreciate. For example, knowing your download and usage patterns help us design better lessons for you in the future. Also, having your contact information will allow us to inform you of our latest news and product information, as well as any special offers, like free new lessons. The information we collect can be grouped into three different types:

1\. **Personal Details** : This is information you provide us with, such as your name, email, city of residence, and other personal information you provide when you fill out your profile.  
2\. **Your Usage Patterns** : When you use our site, we collect data on your patterns, such as when and how often you log-in, which lessons you download, which pages you visit most on our site, etc.  
3\. **Your Communicative Record** : We store all records of any communicative activity (with us or other Deep English members). 

**Mailing List**  
Deep English runs an opt-in mailing list for learners who are interested in or who have purchased Deep English lessons. We use the mailing list to communicate directly with our members and at-large community, notifying them of our latest developments, promotions, free lessons, learning tips, and other product and service recommendations. All of our mailing lists are optional, meaning that subscribers can choose to unsubscribe if they wish with a simple click of their mouse. We place an unsubscribe link in every single email we send out on the mailing list, making it easy for people to stop receiving our messages at any time.

**Use of Cookies**  
Like most other websites, Deep English uses a standard technology called ‘cookies’ to collect information on how our website is used and to make the user experience better and more convenient. A cookie is just a very small text document which – if your browser permits it – our website will place on your computer. The cookie helps us recognize you when you visit our site. Please understand that cookies DO NOT allow us to collect any other private information about you. They are essentially harmless in that respect.

**Server Logs**  
We use standard web server logs to study how our site is used. This type of information can include your date and time of visit, your I.P. address, how many pages you viewed and how long you were on each page, and the website visited just before and just after our website, etc. 

**Protection of Your Information**  
Deep English takes extensive measures to safeguard your personal information against misuse, lost, theft, and unauthorized access, disclosure, and destruction. In addition, all financial transactions are handled via PayPal, which is a highly secure payment processor. 

NOTE: WE WILL NEVER SHARE YOUR INFORMATION WITH NOR SELL ANY OF YOUR INFORMATION TO A THIRD PARTY. Your private, personal information is for our use only, and is safe and secure with us.

**Questions about Privacy**  
If you have any questions concerning how we collect your personal information and what we do with it, please [contact us](http://deepenglish.com/contact).
